Smells kind of weird in here today,
yeah? It's not me.
Um why did you take Cody Ford?
Um was he just already you said for
years if if you're open you'll you'll
throw him the ball.
Yeah, I was I was thinking Jamarr and
then safety played it pretty good. So, I
just progressed outside to Cody.
I threw it to him early early in the
week in practice kind of as a joke, but
that's just how the play played out. Um
what were your what was your reaction
when they said, "Hey, we got to play for
Cody?" Maybe not for Cody like you said,
but a play with Cody in the game plan.
I'm always for fun stuff like that.
Number one,
you know, defense kind of keeps them off
balance.
Number two, it's just fun.
Was that your first read or was Jamarr
your first read?
I was going to Jamarr first, but
um
then I checked Drew.
Didn't work out.
And I side to Cody. What did you think
of Cody with I'm sorry, but
What did you think of Cody with ball in
his hands? Couldn't believe what I was
watching.
>> [laughter]
>> But it was sick.
Have you ever seen him play basketball
or anything or
Nope.
Have not. What did you think the offense
was all in all today?
I thought we were pretty pretty
productive. Pretty efficient.
I thought we were
I'll Chase Brown was great. He's been
great all year.
Made plays when we had to, but
stayed on schedule, converted third
downs. I thought it was a
efficient performance.
Cody just told us he was a tight end in
middle school and freshman year. You see
the the roots of that on that I do. I
do. I do. Long long time ago.
Many [laughter] moons ago, but I do.
With Chase Brown, he was phenomenal to
close last season, but have you even
seen him take the next step this year?
Yeah, he just keeps getting better. He
last year he hit a level that
you know, once you hit that level then
you're just
continuous improvement in all areas of
your game. There was he didn't have any
weaknesses last year. And he just
stepped up a notch this year. It's been
fun to watch. How did you play Chase the
third the third and 20 given sacked
twice and when you gave it to him on the
third and 20 I are you thinking, "Hey,
take it and get it as close to field
goal range?" You can't what was going
through your mind?
Yeah, we just called a screen there.
Um
just trying to get it out of our hands
and you know, he made a play, got us in
a field goal range, got us points. That
was big play in the game.
Over the last two weeks in the third
quarter Chase Brown now has a combined
five touchdowns. Is there any rhyme or
reason to that you think? No, that's
just how it plays out.
Joe, there's always a lot of talk of
meaningless football. Does this What
meaning does this kind of game have when
you have this kind of performance, you
know, and and do what y'all did today?
Yeah, that's
you know, every time we go out there
we're putting our bodies on the line and
going out and
trying to prove ourselves in front of
the world.
Playoffs are
out of the question obviously, but
anytime you step foot out there you're
playing for pride, playing for your guys
and and trying to execute and trying to
put good stuff on tape. Is there a part
of y'all that wants to send a message
that, "Hey, we might be out of it this
year, but next year we feel like we can
do something." Is that Um I mean every
every year is
so new, new players, new team,
new schemes.
We're just trying to go and play well
right now. I know you're not watching
every snap of the defense. You're
looking at that kind of all of those
things, but for them to to perform the
way they did against a good offense
today, what does that mean? Yeah, we we
tackled well, we stopped the run.
And
when you do those two things
then you get to third down and you know,
anything can happen on third down. So,
the key is stopping the run and we've
done that for for several weeks in a row
now.
Uh it's been fun to watch. How have you
seen Miles
develop, change have you in practice?
Obviously, he's he's been far more
productive over the past few months.
Yeah, he's always he's always been a
good practice player, practices hard.
Just impacting the game.
You know, like I said earlier this week
I don't I don't know anything about his
specific gap responsibilities or
on any specific players. I just see him
around the football, around the
quarterback, making plays, hitting
people, impacting the game in a lot of
different ways. It's been fun to watch.
When you throw the ball to Jamarr on a
bubble screen like the touchdown, you
have the ball out of your hands, kind of
how fun is that to watch what he does
next? Yeah, that's
that's just icing on the cake for me.
And
my job is to get
playmakers
the ability to to make plays, get the
ball in their hand and
you can't you spend a lot of time
throughout the week, coaches do, trying
to
find ways to
get our guys the ball in space. You can
scheme it up a lot of different ways.
This is just one there is try to figure
out a way to put Jamarr one-on-one with
a corner and
it was good well-designed play and
obviously, you know, Jamarr's great.
First of all,
when did you think on that play during
it, "Oh, he's scoring?" As soon as he
made the first guy miss, I knew he was
going to score.
What's that dynamic like? Obviously, you
and Jamarr it's been talked about so
much, you're so close from college, etc.
But when he's going through a touchdown
drought and he has all this belief in
you and you have all this belief in him,
what's that like in the week leading up
to games?
Uh I didn't even realize he was in a
touchdown drought.
You know, he's he's the same guy every
day.
For the most part. Mornings
sometimes he's a little tired, but once
we get out to practice he's the same guy
every day and
um
just goes about his business and
goes and produces on Sundays and plays
great and
figures out a way to to get open against
very very unique
technique from defenses. And he's seen
it all now, so he knows what he's doing
in all those different looks.
And
you know, everybody's game plan is
focused around him and not letting him
beat him and he continuously just
produces at a high level, so
that's not an easy thing to do and I
don't see any other
receivers in the league that get the
attention that he does. Joe, you were
going off a question that Ben asked.
He's We're talking about new schemes,
new players at the start of each season.
I'm wondering if there's anything about
the kind this kind of late season
momentum
that can carry over into the next
season. It sounds like you think
a lot of things start from zero, but is
anything transferable? I just think
individual
growth
is transferable.
When you have
young guys starting to impact the game
at a high level for the first time,
you have to carry that through the off
season.
Cuz it's not just
just cuz you do it one year doesn't mean
it's going to happen the next year.
The guys that
can build off of individual performances
and growth from the year before are the
ones that end up being great players.
Uh the ones that know how to
change their body, change their
techniques to improve from the year
before. Um that's what you're looking
for. How much did you miss this feeling
while you were out this season?
Yeah, this is why you this is why you do
it.
The
highs and lows, the emotion.
It's performing with your guys. It's uh
it's what you love about it. Yes, sir.
Part of this that that's painful knowing
the level that you're playing now as a
as a team, defense, offense,
everything's coming together and there
there could have been a shot, but there
isn't a shot at We're we're we are where
we're at.
There's nothing we can do about it now
except put one foot in front of the
other and
try to get better, go and perform again
next week. How
There've been times throughout your
career where you probably had offensive
lineman coming up to you asking for the
ball. I mean, what did it mean I don't
know how many passes you've thrown
offensive lineman in your time here in
Cincinnati, but did it what did it feel
like to finally, you know, get one of
those guys the ball? Yeah, we tried one
to Mimms last year, had to throw it
away.
I think this is this is probably the
first one that I've thrown and you know,
we've had play play designs for it in
the past, but anytime you can get the
ball in those guys' hands,
they just light up like a kid on
Christmas. It's pretty fun to watch. Has
there been an offensive lineman you met
that wasn't didn't want the ball? No,
they all want they all want it.
>> [laughter]
>> Have you ever in your career played that
before to an offensive lineman?
You can go back to like high school. Um
not that I can remember. Yeah, I was
just wondering.
More surprised at Cody after the catch
or Sam's diving touchdown?
Last I mean, they're both tough plays.
>> I think I think Cody after the catch for
sure.
>> [laughter]
>> Thanks, Joe.
Yeah, thanks, Joe.
>> [clears throat]